Guide to the Steele Ranch Records, 1855-1973
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES K. NON-ORIGINAL MATERIAL (XEROXES, REPORDUCTIONS, ETC.)
  - Correspondence. (Box 72, Folder 333)
  - Genealogy. (Box 72, Folder 334-335)
  - Maps and diagrams. (Box 72, Folder 336)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 72, Folder 337-338)
  - Xeroxes of newsclipping. (Box 72, Folder 339)
- SERIES L. CATHERINE STEELE'S MANUSCRIPT NOTES
  - Año Nuevo. (Box 73, Folder 340-342)
  - Cortez. (Box 73, Folder 343)
  - Cow Heaven. (Box 73, Folder 344)
  - Sir Francis Drake. (Box 73, Folder 345)
  - Explorers. (Box 74, Folder 346-347)
  - Genealogy. (Box 74, Folder 348-349)
  - Graham, Isaac. (Box 74, Folder 350)
  - Grange. (Box 74, Folder 351-352)
  - Green Oaks. (Box 74, Folder 353)
  - Heart's Delight - Col. & Mrs. Roger Fitch. (Box 74, Folder 354)
  - Pigeon Point. (Box 74, Folder 355)
  - Pigeon Point. (Box 75, Folder 356)
  - Ranch del Oso. (Box 75, Folder 357)
  - Pre-Steele history. (Box 75, Folder 358)
  - Steeles of Pt. [UNK] Nuevo. (Box 75, Folder 359)
  - Transportation and communication. (Box 75, Folder 360)
  - Waddell Water System. (Box 75, Folder 361-362)
  - Water matters. (Box 75, Folder 363)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 75, Folder 364-365)
  - Cow Heaven. (Box 76, Folder 366)
  - Miscellnaeous. (Box 76, Folder 367-373)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 77, Folder 374-377)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 78, Folder 378-383)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 79, Folder 384-389)
- SERIES M. C. STEELE'S TYPESCRIPT NOTES
  - Año Muevo. (Box 80, Folder 390-391)
  - Genealogy. (Box 80, Folder 392)
  - Grange matters. (Box 80, Folder 393)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 80, Folder 394-395)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 81, Folder 396-403)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 82, Folder 404-409)
NAME ABBREVIATIONS
A.B.J. A.B. Jackson
A.B.S. A.B. Searle
A.B.W. A. Bryan Williams, Game Commissioner
A.C.P. A.C. Pye
A.E. A. Elder
A.E.C. A.E. Carlson, Acting Chief
A.E.C.* Adolph E. Costella
A.E.O. A.E. O'Donnell, Director
A.G. Allan Grant, President
A.G.B. A.G. Black, Governor
A.J. Alex Johnson
A.J.* Allan Joslin
A.J.L. Andrew J. Lagomarsino
A.J.L.* Arleigh J. Lamie, Assistant Resident Manager
A.K. Adrien Kuffer, Work Unit Conservationist
A.K.* Amelie Kneass, Curator
A.M.F. A.M. Fournier, Assistant Cashier
A.R.I. Albert R. Iness, Ranger I
A.S. A. Stuart
A.S.M. Allen S. Mobley
A.T. Audrey Taylor, Agency Cashier
A.W.S. A.W. Sans, Attorney
A.W.S.* A.W. Spear
A.W.W. A.W. Watson Jr.
B.A. Bob Allen, Sales Manager
B.B. Ben Black
B.B.S. Bert B. Snyder, Attorney
B.C. Bernard Casebolt, Senior Associate
B.D. Betty Donnellan, Underwriter
B.G. Bernice Green, Underwriter
B.H.C. B.H. [Crocheron], Director
B.J.G. Burton J. Goldstein, Attorney
B.K. Biscoe Kibbey
B.L.S. Bruce L. Sharpe, President
B.M. Bernard McCavitt
B.M.H. Barbara M. Hink
B.M.S. Barbara M. Stafford, Claims Examiner
B.S.A. Barney S. Antic, Secretary-Manager
C.A.F. C.A. Farrell
C.A.M. C.A. McCullough, District Engineer
C.A.P. C.A. Palmtag, Assistant Cashier
C.A.R. Charles A. Rummel, Assistant Counsel
C.B. C. Barlow, Secretary-Treasurer
C.B.D. C.B. Day, Manager
C.B.S. Catherine Baumgarten Steele
C.C. Chas. Chesser
C.C.G. Charles C. Gans, M.D., Director
C.D.H. C.D. Holman, Special Agent
C.E.A. C.E. Andrews
C.E.P. C.E. Proctor
C.F.H. C.F. Howland
C.F.H.* C.F. Humphrey
C.F.W. Carl F. Wente, President
C.H. Carl Hoag
C.H.A. Claude H. Adams, Counsel
C.H.A.D. C.H.A. Duke, Assistant Manager
C.H.B. Chester H. Barber, Secretary
C.H.T. C.H. Taylor, Lieutenant (jg)
C.J.S. C.J. Shields, Lieutenant (jg)
C.M.K. C.M. Kennedy, Sales Engineer
C.P.R. C.P. Ralston, Regional Manager
C.R.S. Chloe R. Steele
C.S. Ch_____(?) Sullivan, Herdsman
C.W. Charles Watrous
C.W.L. Chester W. Lebsack, Attorney
C.W.T. C.W. Timmons, Vice-President
C.W.W. C.W. Wikander
D.A. David Atkins
D.B. Mrs. Dennis Barnes, Secretary
D.C. Dorothy Croud, Agency Cashier
D.E.O. D.E. O'Keefe, Proprietor
D.E.S. Dent E. Snider
D.E.W. D.E. Watkins, Secretary & General Manager
D.H. D. Harriman
D.H.H. Dorothy H. Huggins
D.K.M. D.K. Merrill, Manager
D.M. Dorothy McElhinney, Claims Examiner
D.O.M. Donald O. May
D.R.B. D.R. Barber
D.S. Don Sias, Vice-President
E. Elder
E.A.W. Ernest A. Wilson, Attorney
E.B. E. Brunetti, President
E.B.* Eugene Blake Jr., Capt. U.S. Coast Guard
E.B.** Eugene Boone, Production Manager
E.B.B. E.B. Benson
E.B.S. Edgar B. Stuart
E.B.M. E.B. Mason, Office Manager
E.C.B. E.C. Brownlee, Executive Secretary
[E.C.H.] [E. Clyde Harris], Chief
E.C.K. E.C. Killermeyer
E.D. Ed Daubenbis, Vice-President
E.D.H. E.D. Hodge, Right-of-Way Agent
E.D.T. E.D. Taylor
E.E. E. Ewing, Manager
E.E.W. Edward E. Webber
E.F.M. E.F. McGee, Vice-President
E.F.T. Edward F. Treadwell
E.G. Mrs. Elizabeth Gudde, Acquisition Librarian
E.H. E. Harms
E.H.H. Earl H. Harris
E.H.S. Edward H. Siems, Grand Secretary
E.I.G. E.I. Gudelj, Sales Manager
E.J.A. Eugene J. Adams, Attorney
E.J.A.* E.J. Abbott, Secretary
E.J.E. Emile J. Etienne
E.J.M. E.J. McLarney, Deputy Commissioner
E.J.P. Ernest J. Peters, Division Passenger Agent
E.J.W. Edward J. Wickson, Secretary
E.K. Erwin Kellogg
E.L.A. E.L. Anderson
E.L.M. E.L. MaCaulay, Chief of Patrol
E.L.R. Emmet L. Rittenhouse, Attorney
E.M. E. Miller
E.M.* Elaine Millon, Claims Examiner
E.M.** Elizabeth Martinelli, Chief Deputy Registrar
E.M.H. Eugene Mason Howell, Public Health Engineer
E.N. Mrs. Elizabeth Nash
E.N.F. Ella N. Fitch
E.S.A. Ella S. Allen
E.S.M. Edwing S. Moore, Executive Vice-President
E.W.F. E.W. Fraters, Assistant Secretary
E.W.K. E.W. Kay, Secretary-Treasurer
E.W.S. E.W. Swinghy (?)
E.W.S.* Edgar W. Steele
[F.] [Ferrar]
F.A.D. F.A. Dailey
F.A.G. Frank A. Gyorgy, Permit Engineer
F.B. Frank Brandreth, Superintendent
F.C. Francis Caroll, State Director
F.C.* Frank Champion Jr.
F.C. Jr. Franklin Cornell Jr., Secretary
F.D. Frank Delucchi, Secretary
F.E.C. Fred E. Cunha, President of Board of Directors
F.E.N. F.E. Newhagen, Buyer
F.E.R. F.E. Reed, Assistant Secretary
F.M. Frederick Mee
F.M.S. F.M. Stanger
F.N.S. F.N. Steele
F.O.M. F.O. Morris
F.R. F. Ronnebaum, Cashier
F.R.B. F.R. Butter
F.R.F. F.R. Felter, Agent
F.R.H. Frank R. Hodgson, Assistant Secretary
F.S.O. Frank S. Oliver
F.T. Florence Tully, Record Clerk
F.W.S. F.W. Spencer, President
G.A.H. Geo. A. Hayden, Assistant Manager
G.A.T. George A. Townsend, President
G.B. Gus Barbe
G.B.F. Gerald B. Ferrari, Attorney
G.C. Geo. Chalmers, Manager
G.C.G. G.C. Gianda, Manager
G.C.W. G.C. Wickson, Editor
G.F.N. G.F. Niebuhr
G.F.T. Geo. F. Theverkaug
G.G.G. Geo. G. Graham, Chief Clerk
G.G.P. G.G. Parks, Major, Infantry Assistant
G.H. Gerald Haet, Secretary
G.H.C. George(?) H. Cann, District Manager
G.K. [George Kennedy]
G.L.H. Geo. L. Harding, Honorary Curator
G.R.N. Gladys R. Norton
G.S. George Steele
G.S.* Gerald Sheey
G.W.N. G.W. Null, Chief Engineer
G.W.R. George W. Reed, Secretary-Treasurer
H.A.B. Henry A. Bourne, Jr.
H.A.F. H.A. Frew, Office Manager
H.B.W. H.B. Warden, Vice-President
H.C. Harold Conkling, Deputy in Charge of Water Rights
H.C.B. H.C. Bailor
H.St.C.M. Heber St. Clair Mahood
H.D.H. Henry D. Hall
H.E.P. H.E. Pezzoni, Director of Agriculture
H.F.B. H.F. Boyer
H.G.M. H.G. Mathewson, Secretary
H.G.W. H.G. Witt
H.H. Hilda Hagne, Chairman of Artifacts
H.H.H. H.H. Hopkins
H.H.M. [UNK]
H.L. Helen Leahy
H.L.H. Harvey L. Hansen, Secretary
H.M. Hugh Morgan
H.M.* Hulda McLean, Chairman
H.M.S. Herbert M. Sutton, Board Clerk
H.O.H. H.O. Heiner, Vice-President
H.O.R. Howard O. Rose, Assistant Secretary-Treasurer
H.R.E. H.R. Erkel
H.S. Harry Simerly
H.S.G. Hugh S. Gordon, Manager
H.S.M. H.S. Moxley
H.S.R. Harry S. Robinson
H.W.S. H.W. Saunders, Manager
I.B.A. I.B. Adams, Division Manager
I.C.S. Isaac C. Steele
I.G.G. I.G. Gardner, Vice-President
I.G.H. I. G. Heiner
I.H.P. Irving H. Pfaffenberger, Counsel
I.S. Irene Simpson, Director, History Room
I.S.N. Irene Simpson Neasham, Assistant Vice-President & Director
I.W.H. I.W. Hellman, President
[J.A.A.] [J.A. Arata]
J.A.K. J.A. Kellam, Manager
J.B. J. Bofinger, Credit Manager
J.B.* Jack Blanton, Secretary-Treasurer
J.B.F. Joel B. Frantz
J.C.S. John S. Stirrat
J.C.W. J.C. Wagner
J.D. J. Dandley
J.D.B. J.D. Bromfield
J.E.C. J.E. Clancy, Treasurer
J.E.C.* J.E. Costella, Assistant Cashier
J.F. J. Farbstein
J.F.* Mrs. Jean Fassler, Chairman
J.F.M. J. Frank Murphy, Attorney
J.F.W. Jacob F. Wolters
J.H.B. John H. Benson
J.H.B.* John H. Butler
J.H.H. J.H. Hauschildt, Manager
J.J. J. Jorgensen
J.J.J. J.J. Johnson, Resident Agent
J.J.M. J.J. McNamara, County Agent
J.J.M.* J.J. Morey, Cashier (same as J.M.)
J.J.W. J.J. Whearty
J.J.W.* J.J. Wilson
J.K. John Kretich
J.L. John Langer
J.M. J. Morey, Cashier (same as J.J.M.*)
J.M.K. J.M. Kinney, Director Archives Division
J.M.R. J.M. Robertson
J.O.T. J.O. Tobin, Assistant Secretary
J.O.W. J.O. Wilson, Secretary-Treasurer
J.P.B. Julius P. Barclay, Chief
J.P.V. J.P. [Vissien]
J.R. Jesse Robb, Superintendent
J.R.A. J.R. Alcantara
J.R.D. J.R. Delfino,
J.T.C. Jesse T. Chaffe, District Park Superintendent
J.T.D. J.T. Demicheli, Secretary
K.D.F. Kenneth D. Ferguson
K.H. K. Hamada
K.L.W. K.L. Woodward, Chief
L.A.R. Louis A. Rozzoni, President
L.A.R.* Louis A. Ruzicka
L.B.K. Lauretta B. Keeler, Director
L.C. Lawrence Canfield
L.C.D. Mrs. Louisiana Clayton Dart, Curator
L.C.R. L.C. Rausch, District Manager
L.E.W. Leon E. Warmke, Attorney
L.F. L. Flemming, Bookkeeper
L.G.H. Leo G. Hertlein, Associate Curator
L.G.O. L.G. Owens, District Superintendent
L.H.A. L.H. Anderson, Insurance Agent
L.H.L. L.H. Lopes, Vice-President & Cashier
L.K.H. L.K. Hill, Executive Officer
L.N. Lowell Nelson, Chief of Division
L.O.M. Leslie O. Merrill, Executive Director
L.O.W. Leon O. Whitsell, Executive Secretary
L.P.B. L.P. Behrens, Cashier
L.R. Lou Rabe, Registrar-Cataloger
L.R.M. L. R. Moretti
L.R.P. Louis R. Pollack, President
L.S. Louis Sutter, Vice-President & Cashier
L.T.R. Lee T. Ross, Attorney
L.W. Lovell White, Cashier
M.A. Madge Ash
M.B. Marguerite Bullo
M.B.H. [Mildred B_____(?) Hoover]
M.B.R. M.B. Richey
M.E.E. M.E. Edwards, Senior Manager Camp Inspector
M.E.E.* Myron E. Etienne, Attorney
[M.G.W.] [Moo G. Wing], Manager
M.J.L. Max J. Leonard, Commissioner
M.K. Mickey Karpas, Associate Curator
M.K.W. M.K. White
M.M. Mary McHale, Agency Cashier
M.M.F. Milton M. Frincke, District Superintendent
M.M.G. Marian M. Goodman, Staff Writer & Librarian
M.R. Marianda Roberts
M.S.D. Marjorie S. Dellamonica, Secretary
M.T. Margaret Titcomb, Librarian
M.T.S. M. T. Silva
N.B.S. Norwood B. Smith
N.G.B. N.B. van da Bos, President
N.M. Neil McPherson
N.W.G. N.W. Gilchrist, Local Representative
O.A.K. O.A. Kady
O.B.L. O.B. Larsen, President
O.N.S. Osman N. Steele
O.O. Oliver Olsen, Secretary
O.O.O. O.O. Orr, Manager
O.W.K. Oliver W. Kilham, Sales Engineer
P.L.H. Philip L. Hicks
P.M.P. P.M. Paulson
P.N. Pamela Nielson
P.T.G. Paul T. Gallagher
P.W. Jr. P. Wilson Jr., Cashier
P.Z. Peter Zadelovich, Assistant Cashier
R.A.N. Ralph A. Nissen, Chairman, Executive Committee
R.B. Ralph Brown
R.B.B. R.B. Burmister, Cashier
R.B.M. Richard B. Morris
R.C. R. [Campi]
R.D. Rosemary Duggin, Planner III
R.D.B. R.D. Barkie
R.E.S. Renesselar E. Steele
R.F.K. R.F. Kretz
R.G. Mrs. Roger Cummings, President
R.G.D. R.G. Dusky
R.G.S. R.G. Stevenson, General Superintendent
R.H. R. Henderson, District Manager
R.H.B. R.H. Brown
R.H.H. R.H. Hamilton, Secretary
R.H.H.* R.H. Henwood, Manager
R.H.S. R.H. Sciaroni, Farm Advisor
R.H.S.* Ralph H. Shaw, Director
R.H.T. Rex H. Turner, Assistant to President
R.J.B. R.J. Burrowes
R.J.N. R.J. Norris
R.J.S. R. J. Seller, President
R.K. Ralph Kenworthy, Assistant Production Manager
R.L.A. Mrs. R.L. Adkins, Membership Secretary
R.M.W. R.M. Welch, Assistant, Cashier
R.S.L. Reginald S. Laughlin
R.S.S. R.S. Shainwald, Secretary
R.T. Roland Tognazzini, President
[R.]W.A. [R.]W. Anderson
R.W.R. R.W. Randall, Superintendent
R.W.R.* Robert W. Reese, State Park Historian I
S.B.C. S.B. Cooksley
S.E.B. Susan E. Burns, Researcher
S.G.L. Sidney G. Lang, Area Supervisor
S.H.D. S.H. Dado, Assistant Chief
S.I.R. Shirley I. Rowe, Accountant
S.K.A. S.K. Annand, President
S.L.T. S.L. Thrash, President
S.P.H. S.P. Hinman, Escrow Supervisor
S.T.L. S_____(?) T_____(?) L_____(?)
S.T.M. S.T. Meyer, Clerk for Trustees
S.V.G. S.V. Gunnison
T.C. Theodore Char
T.E.G. T.E. Gay
T.[J.]M. Ted [J.] Moniz
T.W.B. T.W. Brooks, Assistant Sales Manager
T.W.M. Thomas W. McKnew, Secretary
T.W.S. T.W. Snell, Division Manager
T.Z. Thelma Ziener, State Supervisor
V.R.F. V.R. Frazee, Auditor
W.A.E. Willis A. Evans, Fisheries Management Supervisor
W.B. William Bascom, Director
W.B.M. W.B. Martin
W.C. W_____(?) C_____(?)
W.C.* Walter Carmean, Assistant, Cashier
W.C.D. Walter C. Dean, Secretary
W.D.E. Willard D. Ellis, President
W.D.K. Mrs. W.D. Kunze, Registrar
W.E. William [H.] Enomoto, President (same as W.H.E.)
W.E.D. Wilson E. Denlinger
W.E.H. Walter E. Hettman
W.F.S. William Frederick Steele
W.H.B. W.H. Brainard
W.H.E. William H. Enomoto, President (same as W.E.)
W.H.G. Wm. H. Grul
W.H.H. Wade H. Hoover, Attorney
W.H.M. W.H. Millar
W.H.S. W.H. Smith, Manager Contract Dept.
W.H.S.* Wilfred H. Steele
W.J.G. Wm. J. Glover,
W.L.F. W.L. Fottrell, Investigator
W.N.F. W.N. Finman
W.O.M. Walter O. Manwaring, Assistant Manager
W.R.H. Warren R. Howell
W.S.B. W.S. Bradley, Secretary-Treasurer
W.S.K. W.S. King, Collection Manager
W.S.L. Wm. S. Lynch Jr., Assistant Comptroller
W.T.C. Willis T. Chapman, Manager
W.T.J. W.T. Jyrinki
W.U.F. Walter U. Friendrichs
W.W.B. W.W. Budge
W.W.H. W.W. Hopper, Vice-President
Z.L.C. Zach Lamar Cobb, Co-Chairman